<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><metadata>
    <idinfo>
        <citation>
            <citeinfo>
                <title>Districts - Voter Precincts</title>
                <onlink>https://gisdata.pima.gov/arcgis1/rest/services/GISOpenData/Boundaries/MapServer/8</onlink>
            </citeinfo>
        </citation>
        <descript>
            <abstract>https://gis.pima.gov/data/contents/metadet.cfm?name=distvote</abstract>
            <purpose>Districts - Voter Precincts</purpose>
        </descript>
        <spdom>
            <bounding>
                <westbc>-113.34999999999809</westbc>
                <eastbc>-110.39999999999816</eastbc>
                <northbc>32.549999999999436</northbc>
                <southbc>31.40999999999946</southbc>
            </bounding>
        </spdom>
        <keywords>
            <theme>
                <themekt>None</themekt>
                <themekey>Pima County</themekey>
                <themekey>boundaries</themekey>
                <themekey>districts</themekey>
                <themekey>precincts</themekey>
                <themekey>GIS Open Data</themekey>
            </theme>
        </keywords>
        <accconst>None</accconst>
        <useconst>GIS Data and Products Disclaimer: 

We give no warranty, expressed or implied, as to
the accuracy, reliability, or completeness of the data. This disclaimer applies both to the direct
use of the data and any derivative products produced with the data.

Any type of boundary, linear or point locations
contained within this data, or displayed within this product, are approximate,
and should not be used for authoritative or legal location purposes. Users should independently research,
investigate, and verify all information to determine if the quality is
appropriate for their intended purpose. If legally-defensible boundaries or locations are required, they should
first be established by an appropriate state-registered professional.

The information contained in the data is dynamic
and may change over time. It is the
responsibility of the data user to use the data appropriately and consistent
with the intent stated in the metadata. In particular, this Open Data version
of the dataset is intended for use either as a Shapefile download, or as a
service within a map or private application. It is not intended for use as a
service within another public-facing application.

Per A.R.S. 37-178: A public agency that shares geospatial data of which it is the
custodian is not liable for errors, inaccuracies or omissions and shall be held
harmless from and against all damage, loss or liability arising from any use of
geospatial data that is shared.</useconst>
        <datacred>Pima County Information Technology Department - Geographic Information Systems, 33 N Stone Av, 15th Floor, Tucson, AZ 85701</datacred>
    </idinfo>
    <metainfo>
        <metd>20200227</metd>
        <metc>
            <cntinfo>
                <!--no contact person or organization name available-->
            </cntinfo>
        </metc>
        <metstdn>FGDC Content Standard for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn>
        <metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv>
        <mettc>local time</mettc>
    </metainfo>
</metadata>
